American Association for Labor Legislation Pamphlet File 5001 PAM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 2, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Some Effects of the Law Licensing Fee-Charging Employment Bureaus, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Annual Department Report of Cleveland State-City Employment Service, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Law Relating to State Employment Bureau and Employment Agencies, 1925; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Author: A.L. Urick
  - Item 9: Illinois Free Employment Office Act, 1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Promoting Good Will- Securing Business for the Public Employment Service, 1927; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Author: B.C. Seiple
  - Item 11: Sixteenth Annial Convention of The International Association of Public Employment Services, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Fitting Capacity to Oppurtunity a message to employers, 1925; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Fitting Capacity to opportunity a message to employers, 1925; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Report of the Farm Labor Division U.S. Employment Service, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Report of the Farm Labor Division U.S. Employment Service, 1925; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: The Labor Situation, 1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: Outline of Plan for Re-Evaluated Program of National Information Bureau, 1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Progress Report on Public Works and Employment Stabilization, 1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 19: Resolutions, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: Bulletin No. 1, 1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Supplement to Bulletin No. 1 of the Coordinating Committee of Employment Activities of New York City, 1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 22: Bulletin No. 2 of the Coordinating Committee of Employment Activities of New York City, 1921; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 23: Securing Employment for the Handicapped, 1927; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Author: Mary La Dame
  - Item 24: Public Employment (Your) Service, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 25: Employment Offices Co-ordination Act, 1926; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 26: Minutes of Conference on Licensing and Inspection of Employment Agencies, 1925; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 27: Employment Agencies, 1928; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Box: 2, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Development of a Federal Public Employment System in the United States, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Author: Fred C. Croxton
  - Item 2: Employment Agencies Officially Exposed; Sworn Testimony Shows Urgent Need of State Action, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: An Ordinance Regulating Private Employment Agencies, 1929; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Directory of Public Employment Offices, 1929; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Monthly statistics of non-profit-making employment bureaus, Mar., 1928- June, 1929, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Bureau of Employment, 1929; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Railroads Labor Agencies Commissaries, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Box: 2, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Private Employment Agencies in New York City, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: Grace A. Comins
  - Item 2: Employment Agencies Survey, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: Walter D. Britt
  - Item 3: Junior Placement Bureau, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Specifications for the State Advisory Council on Employment Problems, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Report of Activities of Bureau of Employment for Period February 1st- June 1st, 1930, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: Fritz Kaufmann
  - Item 6: Report of The Advisory Committee on Employment Problems, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: F.A. Silcox
  - Item 7: Recommendations for a State Program with Respect to Employment Agencies Adopted by New York Association of Commercial Employment Agencies, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Extract from Address May 1, 1930, by President Hoover before the Chamber of Commerce of the United States, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Minutes of the Meeting of State Advisory Council on Employment Problems, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: Bryce M. Stewart
  - Item 10: Monthly Statistics of non-profit-making employment bureaus, January, 1929 - March, 1930, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: Confidential, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Fee-Charging Job Agencies in New York State Need State Supervision, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Author: Frances Perkins
  - Item 13: Fee-Charging Job Agencies in New York State Need State Supervision, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 14: Fee-Charging Job Agencies in New York State Need State Supervision, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: Monthly Statistics of non-profit-making employment bureaus October, 1929 - September, 1930, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: Monthly Statistics of non-profit-making employment bureaus October, 1929 - October, 1930, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 17: Statistics of Non-Profit-Making Employment Bureaus in New York City, 1930; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Box: 2, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: An Analysis of Its Organization and Operation, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Job Study of Waitresses Oppurtunities for Waitresses in New York City, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Progress Report, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Author: France Perkins
  - Item 4: statement on Public Employment Offices Submitted to The Conference of Governors of Seven Eastern States at Albany, January 23, 1931, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Box: 2, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Preliminary Survey of the Problem of Discrimination Against Jews in Employment in New York City, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Author: Elinor Sachs Barr
  - Item 2: An Industrial Survey of the Needle Trades to Determine a Vocational Guidance Policy for Young Men of Jewish Descent With Regard to the Industry, 1931; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Box: 2, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: High Points in the Development of the Public Employment Center of Rochester, 9132; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Author: Jess T. Hopkins
  - Item 2: Division of Junior Placement, 1932; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Author: Clare E. Lewis
- Box: 2, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Story of the Emergency Work Bureau, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Author: W.H. Matthews
  - Item 2: The Story of the Emergency Work Bureau, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Report of Conference on Public Employment Office Problems, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Types of Office, Premises and Equipment, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Local Advisory Councils, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Personnel of the State Employment Service, 1933; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Box: 2, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Text of Act of June 6, 1933, " To Provide for the Establishment of a National Employment of a National Employment System and for Cooperation with the States in the Promotion of Such System, and for Other Purposes" and Maximum Amounts Available to the Stat, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Reports of Chairman of State Advisory Council and Standing Committees Virginia State Employment Service, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Minutes of the State Advisory Council, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: "The New Place of Public Employment Service in the Community", 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Analysis of the Staff Employment Agency Laws in the United States as of January 1, 1935., Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Box: 2, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Memorandum on a Suggested Plan of Organization of Advisory Councils for Employment Service and Unemployment Insurance Administration, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Minutes of Meeting of the Federal Advisory Council United States Employment Service, 1936; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Box: 3, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Suggestive Resolution on Federal Regulations of the Interstate Business of Fee-Charging Employment Agencies, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: State of New York Bureau of Employment, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Tentative Program; Nineteenth Annual Convention of The International Association of Public Employment Services United States and Canada, 1931; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Tenatative Program; Nineteenth Annual Convention, 1931; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Please Hand This to the Person Who Engages Your Help, 1909; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Schedule of Fees or Charges To Be Posted in a Conspicuous Place in Office of Agency, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Square Pegs in Square Holes, 1930; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: M.B.S.
  - Item 8: Laundries - South Brooklyn - Victoria, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Emplyment Agencies, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Annual Report, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Arthur A. Quinn
  - Item 11: Employment Agencies, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Employment Agencies, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Employment Agency Renewals, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Employment Agents, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: E.A., 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Employment Agents, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Employment Agencies, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Addresses, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Employment Agents, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Wednesday June 27th, 1934., Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Wednesday, June 13, 1934., Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Hearings - Wednesday, June 20th, 1934., Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Employment Agencies, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Supplement Description of Positions in Social Agencies Executive Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: List of Members, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: List of Members, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Vocational Service Agency, 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Agenda for Meeting of the State Advisory Council, 1937; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Experts, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: All who are not members or who are not on other list in:, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Division V - Industrial and Economic Problems, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Concurrent Resolution of the Senate and Assembly, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Standardization - what it is doing for industry, 1924; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Box: 3, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Engineer, The Cripple and The New Education, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Annual Meeting American Engineering Council of Federated American Engineering Societies, 1924; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Resolutions Authorizing Renewal of Public Works Campaign, 1923; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Objects, 1931; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Address Delivered Before The Philadephia Engineers' Club, 1920; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: Robert B. Wolf
  - Item 6: MC 807, 1930; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: P.G. Agnew
  - Item 7: The Engineering Index Service, 1930; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Work of the American Engineering Standards Committeee, 1921; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Unification of Wire and Sheet Metal Gages Proposed, 1926; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Box: 3, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report on the Work of the State Inspectors of Health, 1907-1908 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Factory and Workshop Act, 1901 Regulations for Use of Horsehair, 1901-1910 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Brief Instructions Concerining Factory Inspection Law, 1907; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: O.P. Hoff
  - Item 4: Specifications and Materials, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: J.H. Morgan
  - Item 5: Specifications and Materials, 1902; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Suggestions Relating To Inspection of Factories, Etc., 1913; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Interpretations of the Ohio State Building Code Relative to Standard Ventilating Stoves, 1913; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: Thomas P. Kearns
  - Item 8: We Recommend:, 1910; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Report on the Inspection of Factories Making Army and Navy Uniforms, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Delegates for the Convention of the International Association of Factory Inspectors, 1913; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Box: 3, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the Director of Investigation on the Confectionery Industry oin New York City, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: Howard B. Woolston
  - Item 2: Paper on The Best Method of Establishing Proper Co-operation Between Employer, Employee and Inspector, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: John J. Hanlon
  - Item 3: Instructions for the Inspection of Plants Where Aniline is Produced or Handled, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: John Roach
  - Item 4: Safety Standards for Insecticides, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Safety Standards for the Manufacture of Lithopone, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Safety Standards for Cutting Oils, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Approved Working Practices in Steam Power Laundries, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Sanitary Standards for the Felt Hatting Industry, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Safety Standards for the Manufacture of Nitro and Amido Compounds, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Sanitary and Engineering Industrial Standards, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Safety Code Administered by Dept. of Labor, State of New Jersey, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Laws Administered by the Dept. of Labor, State of New Jersey, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Compressed Air Law, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Inspection of Mines and Quarries, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Bakeries and Confectionaries Law, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Approval of Plans, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Laws Administered by the Dept. of Labor, State of New Jersey, 1912; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Laws Administered by the Dept. of Labor, State of New Jersey, 1904; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Laws administered by the Dept. of Labor of New Jersey, 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Laws Administered by the Dept. of Labor. State of New Jersey, 1911; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Laws Administered by the Dept. of Labor., 1911; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Basic Code for Dust Control Scope, 1912; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: General Inspection, 1917; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: J.J. McSherry
  - Item 24: Taking Stock in an Employment Department, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: Mary Gilson
  - Item 25: Memoranda Regarding Outstanding Activities of the New York State Industrial Commission, 1921; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Fake "Inspectors" Fleecing Factories, 1930; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Inspection of Industrial Establishments, 1930; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: James L. Gornon
- Box: 3, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Copy of An Act to promote the Public Health by protecting certain employes in this State from the dangers of occupational diseases, and providing for the enforcement thereof., 1911; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Factory Inspection Standards and Qualifications for Factory Inspectors, 1939; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Truck Acts, 1831-1896 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: State Legislation Concerning Wood Alcohol, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Frank Allport
  - Item 5: The Value of Careful Factory Inspection, 1922; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Question of Housekeeping in Our Shops and Factories, 1922; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Phosphorus Poisoning, 1913; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Waldo Peck Adams
  - Item 8: "What Quality of Approach Obtains Best Results", 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: C. C. Foster
  - Item 9: Memorandum for Commissioner Andrews, 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: James L. Gernon
  - Item 10: "The Technique which most Affects The Industrial Executive", 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Visiting Inspector's Responsibility as seen by the Plant Executive, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Lt. Col. Henry A. Reninger
  - Item 12: Number of New York State Factories Employing Less ThaN 10 Persons, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: The Visiting Investigator's Responsibility as Seen By The Plant Executive, 1932; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Henry A. Reninger
  - Item 14: Memorandum for Commissioner Andrews:, 1935; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: James Gernon
  - Item 15: The early diagnosis of Industrial lead-poisoning., 1898; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: S. King Alcock
  - Item 16: News, 1938; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: State Inspection of Factories, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: The Industrial Executive's Responsibilities As Seen by the Visiting Inspector, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: C.E. Pettibone
- Box: 3, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Liberalization of Federal Policies, 1939; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: John A. Kratz
  - Item 2: Minutes of Meeting of Committee on Vocational Rehabilitation of the Federal Advisory Council United States Employment Service, 1933; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Training for Disabled in Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: National Committee for the Disabled, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Salvaging the Injured Worker, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: This Bill Should Pass (S. 4922-H.R. 12880), 1919; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Tentative Statement Regarding The National Committee for the Disabled (Confidential), 1923; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: R.C. Branion
  - Item 8: National Conference on Vocational Rehabilitation of Persons Disabled in Industry or Otherwise, 1922; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Salvage Material is not Wasted, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Men With "Hand" Handicaps, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Linotype Operators in Demand, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Invitation to The National Conference on Rehabilitation of Physically Disabled Persons, 1934; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Massachusetts Pointsfor Consideration and Conclusions, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: Otis Robertson
  - Item 14: Social Medicine and Miscellany, 1918; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Proposals for Revision of Policies Governing Use of Matched Funds, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Vocational Training Division, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Employment of the Handicapped, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Tentative Staatement Regarding The National Committee for the Disabled (Confidential), Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: R.C. Branton
- Box: 3, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Sixty-Six Years of Medical Legislation, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Frederick R. Green, M.D.
  - Item 2: Bulletin 30, 1909; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Sickness Insurance, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Reports on the Poor Law, 1909; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Sir John E. Gorst, Bart., K.C.
  - Item 5: Industrial Conditions in Topeka, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Zenas L. Potter
- Box: 3, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Periodic Physical Examination of Employes, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Eugene Lyman Fisk, M.D.
  - Item 2: Revised By-Laws, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: W.L. Chandler
  - Item 3: The head of Pay Clinics for Persons of Moderate Means., 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Richard C. Cabot, M.S.
  - Item 4: Sickness Insurance: A Bibliography, October 1913, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Margaret Blanche Lyle
  - Item 5: The Survey, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Special Supplement on The Working of the Insurance Act, 1914; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The Physician's Compensation in Co-Operative Practice, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Sickness Insurance a Preventive of Charity Practice, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: B.S. Warren
- Box: 3, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Stenographic Record, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Health Insurance In Its Relation to Public Health, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: I.M. Rubinow
  - Item 3: The Reaction of the British Health Insurance Upon Existing Charities, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: Olga. S. Halsey
  - Item 4: Report of Committee Studying, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Labor vs. Its Barnacles, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: Samuel Gompers
  - Item 6: Discussion of A.W. Whitney's Paper - Proposed Legislation for Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: Dr. F. L. Hoffman
  - Item 7: Resolution No. 88, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: Delegate G.W. Perkins
  - Item 8: Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Preliminary Report of the A.M.A. Medical Committee to the Social Insurance Committee, 1915; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Social Insurance Series Pamphlet No. 3, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Medical Econommist, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Medical Organization Under Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: Alexander Lambert
  - Item 3: Social Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Health Insurance, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Weekly Bulletin of the Department of Health City of New York, 1916; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)